Brophy, John, Papers /4093
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John Brophy Papers
1948-1957
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brophy, John
/4093
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
7984559
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 16, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4093: John Brophy Papers 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records on Microfilm 5277: Workers Education Bureau of America Records 5316: NWLB Records 5418 mf: Committee for Industrial Organizations Minutes on Microfilm 5425 mf: Katherine Pollack Ellickson Papers on Microfilm 5619: ACWA Records 5760 mf: American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5780/002: ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/166 PUBS: ILGWU Education Department Publications 5831 mf: The CIO Files of John L. Lewis, Pt. II: CIO General Files on Microfilm 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6218: Melvyn Dubofsky Papers
Brophy, John
7984559
- 6th Training Specialists Institute (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Profit Sharing Conference II, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  May 1953
- Student Profiles (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National leadership Devel. Conf., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Atherton, Bill (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Beach, Dale (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bella (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bella, Salvatore (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bird, Donald Alan (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bentkowski, John (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Black, Gladys (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Block, Herman (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Burnham, Loron (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Butler, Harold (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Callis, John L. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cantone, Donald C. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Chabon, Robert Samuel (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cleary, Wm. H. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Collins, Alan Keith (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Connally, Claude James (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Curtis, Bryon W. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Custis, Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 22)
- De Angelis, Donald (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Decker, R. M. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Dee, Lillian (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Deveny, John (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Dudley, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Dunsker, Philip W. (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Earle, Wendell (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Ellison, William N. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Evans, Nanie Rudd (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Finder, Robert (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Fingar, L. J. (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Flight, Richard (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fox, Raymond T. (Minor) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Freer, Jeanne (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Fried, Sheldon (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Fries, William (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Gavett, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Gehrig, George (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Glassberg, Richard H. (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Halan, John Paul Hudcovich (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Halsband, Jerome (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Hamm, Erwin (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Held, Paul (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Helsby, Robert D. (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Henry, Donald F. (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Henry, James Gregory (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Hershey, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Higgins, Douglas, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Irving, William (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Jervis, William (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Jones, Donald F. - Alfred Tech Institute (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Jones, Merwin M. (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Jweid, Anthony (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Kapur, Nawal (Box 1, Folder 56)
- King, L. E., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Kirby, Kenneth (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Klett, Richard Z. (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Knipp (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Kooch, Walton (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Landes, Harold B. (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Lapp, Julius (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Lareau, Ernest (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Lentz, Edith (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Levinson (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Lewis, Gerde (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Lewis, William (Box 1, Folder 68)
- McGarrah, Robert (Box 1, Folder 69)
- McLaughlin, Robert (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Mahaney, Francis (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Manchester, Katherine (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Martin, Richard Francis (Minor) (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Melbin, Murray (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Miller, Frank (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Mills, George J. (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Oglesby, Benjamin (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Peevers, Alfred J. (Jr.) (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Peterson, Eleanor (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Piker, Fred K. (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Pulhamus, William (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Quetsch, Cacilie (Box 1, Folder 82)
- 4th Institute for Training Specialists (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Profit Sharing Conference I, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Division of Vocational Education (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Questions on Employment of School-Age Youth (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Let Pupils Learn and Earn (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Digest of Class Reports - ILR 634 SS, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Forms (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Thos. D. Bailey (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Essex County Vocational Schools Official Programs of Studies (Box 2, Folder 9)
- List of Students Who Have Received Degrees with Major in Industrial Education (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Committee on Industrial Education, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Planning Memos - Industrial Education (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Memoranda from State Education Department (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Follow-up Data-Voc.-Ind. Grads. Class of '53, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Industrial Education - Technical Institutes (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Planning Notes (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ILR 364 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Ind. Ed. Directories (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Courses of Study and Student Programs (Box 2, Folder 19)
- The Future of Industrial Education at Cornell (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Jack Griffin (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Voc. Ind. Cooperative Programs, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Diversified Occupational Training (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Nominations and Elections Committee (Box 2, Folder 24)
- VITA - Summer Session, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Communication of Organizational Changes (Box 2, Folder 26)
- VITA, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- VITA, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- VITA (Box 2, Folder 29)
- VITA, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- VITA, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Decentralized Employee Training - Donalds (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Professional Degrees Committee (Box 2, Folder 33)
- NORTH ATLANTIC REG. CONF., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- 10th Annual Conference of Training Dir. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Annual Conf. Of Training Directors 11th (Box 3, Folder 2)
- TRANSPARENCIES - Types and How Made (Box 3, Folder 3)
- TRANSPARENCIES - Materials for Making (Box 3, Folder 4)
- TRANSPARENCY MASTER COPY (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 6th Annual Institute for Training Special (Box 3, Folder 6)
- TRANSPARENCIES - Human Relations (Box 3, Folder 7)
- TRANSPARENCIES - Duplicates (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Information on Conference Speakers (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 7th Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 10)
- TRAINING SPECIALISTS INST., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Institute Speakers (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Institute Announcement Info. Forms (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Annual Conferences of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 14)
- 2nd Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 15)
- 3rd Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Report 8th Annual Conf. Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 17)
- 8th Annual Conf. of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 18)
- 9th Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Post-Conference Reaction Notes (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Notes for Report of 9th Conf. of Training. Dir. (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Request for 9th T.D. Conf. Report (Box 3, Folder 22)
- 5th Annual Institute for Training Specialists (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 6th Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 24)
- 5th Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 25)
- 4th Annual Conference of Training Directors (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 6th Training. Spec. Institute - Evaluation (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Request for Report of 6th Institute for T.S. (Box 3, Folder 28)